<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Homes on Shubham Jain</title>
    <link>https://spjain.github.io/home/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Homes on Shubham Jain</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <copyright>&amp;copy; Shubham Jain</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 20 Apr 2016 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://spjain.github.io/home/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://spjain.github.io/home/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Apr 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://spjain.github.io/home/about/</guid>
      <description>Biography I am a Second Year Graduate Student pursuing Masters in Robotics Engineering at Worcester Polytechnic Institute, Massachusetts. I completed my B.Tech from the Indian Institute of Technology, Kanpur with a minor in Artificial Intelligence. My research interests lie broadly in the fields of Robotics and Computer Vision for solving real world problems.
I am currently working as a Research Assistant under Prof. Emmanuel Agu and in collaboration with UMass Memorial Medical Centre, Worcester for developing a lower extremity wound diagnostics app (Smartwands) that can provide an automatic decision support system for patients.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Projects and Internships</title>
      <link>https://spjain.github.io/home/projects/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Apr 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://spjain.github.io/home/projects/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Relevant Courses</title>
      <link>https://spjain.github.io/home/teaching/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Apr 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://spjain.github.io/home/teaching/</guid>
      <description>I had successfully completed the following courses during my undergraduate study at IIT Kanpur -
 Machine Learning Techniques Recent Advances in Computer Vision Image Processing Data Structures and Algorithms Probabilistic Mobile Robotics Robot Motion Planning Fundamentals of Programming  I am currently taking the following courses at WPI during my graduate studies - Deep Learning for Advanced Robotic Perception, Artficial Intelligence, Foundations of Robotics</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Contact</title>
      <link>https://spjain.github.io/home/contact/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Apr 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://spjain.github.io/home/contact/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>